export const data = [
  {
    question: "What component of a car provides electricity?",
    option1: "Alternator",
    option2: "Ignition Coil",
    option3: "Battery",
    option4: "Generator",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "What shape is the wiring in the ignition system?",
    option1: "Coil",
    option2: "Oddly-Shaped",
    option3: "Circular",
    option4: "Rectangular",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What does HP stand for in terms of power from an engine?",
    option1: "Head Piston",
    option2: "High Performance",
    option3: "Horsepower",
    option4: "High-Powered",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "What does ECU stand for?",
    option1: "Emissions Control Unit",
    option2: "Engine Control Unit",
    option3: "Engine Circular Unit",
    option4: "Element Car Usage",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "What type of plugs are part of a car's ignition system?",
    option1: "Water plugs",
    option2: "Glow plugs",
    option3: "Spark plugs",
    option4: "Fire plugs",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "What type of plugs aren't found in an electric car?",
    option1: "Spark plugs",
    option2: "EV plugs",
    option3: "Kilowatt plugs",
    option4: "all of the above",
    ans: 4,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name given to the tire which bursts as you're driving?",
    option1: "Flat",
    option2: "Pinched",
    option3: "Inflated",
    option4: "Blow out",
    ans: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "The engine control unit is which part of the car?",
    option1: "Transmission",
    option2: "Computer",
    option3: "Braking system",
    option4: "Airbag system",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "You should change what fluid in your car every 5,000 to 10,000 miles?",
    option1: "Engine oil",
    option2: "Blinker fluid",
    option3: "Transmission fluid",
    option4: "Brake fluid",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What type of rings keep the combustion chamber sealed?",
    option1: "Rod",
    option2: "Head",
    option3: "Piston",
    option4: "Crankshaft",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "It is recommended that windshield wipers are changed how often?",
    option1: "Every 5,000 miles",
    option2: "Annually",
    option3: "Every 5 months",
    option4: "Monthly",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "What type of steering makes it easier to turn the wheel?",
    option1: "Mechanical",
    option2: "Pneumatic",
    option3: "Pressure",
    option4: "Power",
    ans: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "In the UK, car tax is based on the emissions of which gas?",
    option1: "Carbon Monoxide",
    option2: "Carbon dioxide",
    option3: "Formaldehyde",
    option4: "Benzene",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "What does a diesel engine use instead of spark plugs?",
    option1: "Water plugs",
    option2: "Glow plugs",
    option3: "Spark plugs",
    option4: "Fire plug",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "What color is the number plate on the back of a UK car?",
    option1: "White & Blue",
    option2: "Blue",
    option3: "Yellow",
    option4: "White",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "What does the A stand for in ABS?",
    option1: "Armored",
    option2: "Absolute",
    option3: "Anti-lock",
    option4: "Arme",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Which pedal do you have to press when changing gear?",
    option1: "Brake",
    option2: "Clutch",
    option3: "Accelerator",
    option4: "Hand-Brake",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "What is needed along with fuel for combustion?",
    option1: "Moisture",
    option2: "Oil",
    option3: "Coolant",
    option4: "Air",
    ans: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "What does the odometer measure?",
    option1: "Mileage",
    option2: "Speed",
    option3: "Temperature",
    option4: "Oil temperature",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What color are brake lights?",
    option1: "Clear",
    option2: "Orange",
    option3: "Red",
    option4: "Amber",
    ans: 3,
  },
];
